https://www.burgerville.com/privacy-policy/

Important announcements regarding COVID-19 & our commitment to your safety. Learn More
Toggle navigation
MenuNutritionThe No. 6LocationsAboutRewardsBlogvilleOrder NowLocationsRewardsBlogvilleOrder NowPrivacy PolicyBurgerville, LLC respects your individual privacy. Our name and reputation have been built on a foundation of trust. This online privacy statement tells you about information collected on our Site, Burgerville.com, how we use the information and how you can opt out of certain information we collect. By using our Site, you are consenting to the information collection practices in this statement.Information Collection and UseBurgerville collects information on the site at two different stages:First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all visitors to the Site. This type of information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of our Site.Second, we require the submission of certain personally identifiable information when you use services that are now or may later become available on the Site. For example, if you communicate with us via email, we will retain the email address and other personal information submitted as part of the communication. Similar information will be collected if you register as a user of the Site, participate in a survey, post content to a forum or subscribe to a newsletter.ContactAboutPrivacy PolicyGift CardsBurger BreaksStoreCareers
Join our email list
Email Address
© Copyright 2020 Burgerville, LLC
